Indiana University President's Office records, 1996-2003 C269
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1996-2003
  - Indianapolis Chamber of Commerce, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 6)
  - Indianapolis Convention and Visitors Association (ICVA) (Box 7)
    - General, 2002-2003 (Box 7)
    - Board Meeting, Feb. 2002; June 2003 (Box 7)
    - ICVA/TTI (Tourism Tomorrow, Inc.), Sept.-Dec. 2002 (Box 7)
  - Indianapolis Cultural Development Commission (Box 7)
    - General, Mar.-May 2003 (Box 7)
    - Meeting, April-June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Indianapolis Marriott Downtown, April 30, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Informatics, Nov. 2002.-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Intellectual Property Policy, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - International Programs, Nov. 2002-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - International Students Fees, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - International Studies, July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Israel, Jerry, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Ivy Tech, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Ivy Tech/USI (University of Southern Indiana) Comments, Jan. 2003 (Box 7)
  - J, general, March-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jacobs, Andy, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Valerie, Jan. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jaffee, Bruce, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jankowski, Jane, March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Janus Ball, March-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Dave, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Stan, April-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Journalism, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Juillerat, Monte, July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Jury Duty, Feb. 2003 (Box 7)
  - K, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kaburaki, Manabu, March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kellum, Paul, May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kelley School of Business, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kenley, Luke, Dec. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Sheila Suess, May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kernan, Joe, Feb. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kinsey Institute, June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Klinker, Sheila, March-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Knight Litigation, April-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Knost, Julie, Feb. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Kornblum, Allan, March 10, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Krauss, John, Feb.; June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Krent, Harold, 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 7)
  - L, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lake Institute Endowment, Jan. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lamkin, Gerald, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Larue Carter/State Board of Health Discussions, Dec. 2002 (Box 7)
  - Law School-Bloomington (Box 7)
    - General, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 7)
    - Dean Search, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Law School-Indianapolis, March-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lefstein, Norm, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Legislative Bills, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Legislative Calendar, Nov. 2002 (Box 7)
  - Legislative Core Committee, Jan-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Legislative Dinners, Jan-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Leibman Tribute Gift and, Feb.-March 2003; May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Leone, Peter-John, April-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lenz, Tom, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lewis, Lynn, June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Liberal Arts, School of (IUPUI/IUB), Dec. 2002; June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Libraries, 2001-2002 Annual Report, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Life Sciences (Box 7)
    - General, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 7)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 7)
    - Initiative, Mar.-May 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lilly Endowment, Jan.-Aug. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lilly Endowment Gift, Dec. 2002; Mar-April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lilly House, Dec. 2002; April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lilly, Ruth, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lisak, Ron, March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Living Legends Dinner, July 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lloyd, Daisy, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lockfield Garden, undated (Box 7)
  - Lofton, Tom, March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Logsdon, Susan, Jan. 10, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Long, Mark, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 7)
  - Long/McRobbie, April 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lovrinic, Joe, Feb. 14, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Lugar Institute, Dec. 2002-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - M, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 7)
  - MacAllister, P.E., May-Dec. 2002 (Box 7)
  - MacDonald, Heather, Jan. 2003 (Box 7)
  - Magrath, Peter, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 7)
  - Mandatory Retirement, Feb. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Mason, Sally Frost, April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Mays, Carolene, Nov. 7, 2002; March 27, 2003 (Box 8)
  - McBride, Angela, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - McBride Celebration, Nov. 2002-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - McGinley, Tim, March 2003; May 2003 (Box 8)
  - McKinney, Bob, March 3, 2003 (Box 8)
  - McNabb, Sara, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - McRobbie, Michael, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - McRobbie/Walker, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Medicine, Winter, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Medicine Research Initiative, undated (Box 8)
  - Meeks, Robert, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Merget, Astrid, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Merten, Jim, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Meslin, Eric, Feb. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Message from Interim President Bepko, Dec. 2002 (Box 8)
  - Midwest Proton Radiotherapy Institute, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Miller, Patrica, March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Minority Participation, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 8)
    Includes material on John Mellencamp
  - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 8)
  - MLK (Martin Luther King) Day (Box 8)
    - Bloomington Community, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
    - IUB, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
    - IUPUI, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Moke, Susan, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Moke/Payne, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Money, John, May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Mooney, Jr., Charles W., Sept. 2002 (Box 8)
  - Morris, Jim, March-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Morton, Ashley, April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Mueller, Rick, March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Music, Feb. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Music, School of, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Multipurpose Science Building, Nov. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - N, general, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nagy, Sarah, April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Najam, Ted, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - National Action Council for Minorities in Engineering, Aug. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - National Association of Minority and Women Owned Law Firms (NAMWOLF), Feb.-Aug. 2003 (Box 8)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant Colleges (NASULGC), Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - National Council for Science and the Environment, March-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - NCA Self-Study, Aug. 2002 (Box 8)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, Feb. 2003 (Box 8)
  - National Science Foundation, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Neale, Bill, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nehf, Jim, March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nelms, Charlie, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nelson, Paul, June 11, 2003 (Box 8)
  - New Indiana, Dec. 2, 2002; Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 8)
  - Notes on Interim Administration, Dec. 2002 (Box 8)
  - Nursing, May-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nursing Search & Screen, Feb. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Nursing, School of, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - O, general, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Occasional Paper No. 48, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - O'Connor, Michael, Jan. 14, 2003 (Box 8)
  - O'Meara, Patrick, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 8)
  - One Book One City, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Opera, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Organizational Ideas, undated (Box 8)
  - P, general, Jan.-Aug. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Jeff, March 2003 (Box 8)
  - P-16, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Palakal, Matthew, May 2003 (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Judy, June-July 2003 (Box 8)
  - Judy Palmer's Data, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - Partnership for Public Service, April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Patchner, Michael, March-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Patterson-Randles, Sandra, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Payne, Sylvia, March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Payton, Bob, April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Pence, Mike, Jan.-Feb. 2003; July 2003 (Box 8)
  - Perrin, Ken, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Perry, Jim, Nov. 2002-April 2003 (Box 8)
  - Person, Ruth, Dec. 2002-July 2003 (Box 8)
  - Pervasive Tech Lab, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, 1999-2003; undated (Box 8)
  - Philanthropic Studies, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Philanthropy, Center on, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Plater Reception, April 2003-June 2003 (Box 8)
  - Policy on Centers and Institutes, undated (Box 8)
  - Pornography Bill, Jan. 2003 (Box 8)
  - POLIS, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Presentation to House and Ways Committee, Jan. 29, 2003 (Box 8)
  - President's Advance, Aug. 1998-July 2003 (Box 8)
  - Presentation to House and Ways Committee, Jan. 29, 2003 (Box 8)
  - President's Cabinet, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 9)
  - President's Cabinet Meeting (Box 9)
    - (IUPUI), Feb. 17, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUB), March 3, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUPUI), March 24, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUB), April 7, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUPUI), April 21, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUPUI), April 28, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUB), May 5, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUPUI), May 19, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUB), June 2, 2003 (Box 9)
  - President's Circle, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
  - President's Informal Advisory Group, Nov. 2002-April 2003 (Box 9)
  - President's Speeches and Talking Points, undated (Box 9)
  - President's Staff Meeting (Box 9)
    - (IUB), Jan. 27, 2003 (Box 9)
    - (IUB), Feb. 3, 2003 (Box 9)
  - President's Update, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 9)
  - Presidential Search, undated (Box 9)
  - Press, I.U., May-June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Promotions, Tenure & Sabbatical Recommendations, March-June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Props, Ken, Mar-April 2003 (Box 9)
  - Provost Position, Jan. 2003 (Box 9)
  - Psychology, April 2003 (Box 9)
  - Psychology Dedication, March 2003 (Box 9)
  - Purdue University (Box 9)
    - Jischke, Martin (Box 9)
      - Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 9)
      - Jan.-June 2003 (Box 9)
      - Trustees, April 29, 2003 (Box 9)
      - Trustees Dinner, March-May 2003 (Box 9)
  - Questions of Costs, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
  - R, general, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 9)
  - Race for the Cure, March-April 2003 (Box 9)
  - RCA Championships Tennis Tournament, June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Real Estate, June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Reauthorization of Higher Education Laws, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
  - Reciprocity, 2001-2002 (Box 9)
  - Reck, Mae, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Recommendation Letters (IU Student Trustee), Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 9)
  - Recommendations, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 9)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 9)
    - Columbus Center, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 9)
    - IUPU Columbus, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 9)
    - East (Box 9)
      - General, Fall 2002-Spring 2003 (Box 9)
      - Campus Visit, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
    - Fort Wayne, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 9)
    - IUPUI (Box 9)
      - General (Box 9)
        - Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 9)
        - June-July 2003 (Box 9)
      - Academic Deans, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 9)
      - Advisory Board, Jan.-Aug. 2003 (Box 9)
      - Clarian, May-Aug. 2003 (Box 9)
      - Council of Dean, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
      - Faculty Council, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
      - IUPUI History, Jan. 2003 (Box 9)
      - Information Sciences Building, April 2003 (Box 9)
      - Law School, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 9)
      - Medical School, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 9)
      - Nursing, April-May 2003 (Box 9)
      - Student Center, Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
    - Kokomo (Box 9)
      - General, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 9)
      - Campus Visit, Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 9)
    - Northwest (Box 9)
      - General, May-July 2003 (Box 9)
      - Campus Visit, Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 9)
      - Review Committee, May 2003 (Box 9)
    - South Bend (Box 9)
      - General, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 9)
      - Campus Visit, Aug.-Dec. 2002 (Box 9)
    - Southeast (Box 10)
      - General, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 10)
      - Campus Visit, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Regional Center Plan Life Sciences Forum, March 2003 (Box 10)
  - Regional Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 10)
  - Registrar, June 2003 (Box 10)
  - Remak, Henry, April 8, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Remnant Trust (Box 10)
    - Oct. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
    - March-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Report to the Community, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Research, 2002-2003 (Box 10)
  - Research and the University Graduate School (RUGS), Jan.-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Responsibility Center Management, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Resume, undated (Box 10)
  - Retention, April-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Retirement Letters (Box 10)
    - A-K, 2003 (Box 10)
    - L-Z, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Retiring Faculty Reception, April 10, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Richardson, F.C., June 2003 (Box 10)
  - Riley Memorial Association (Box 10)
    - Jan.-April 2003 (Box 10)
    - May-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ringel, Bob, March 2003; May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Robbins, Clay, March-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Robbins, Norma, Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Robel, Lauren, April-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ross Endowment, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ruesink, Al, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ruesink/Schneider, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ryan, John, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 10)
  - S, general, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Salaries-Faculty, April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Santini, Gino, Oct. 2002 (Box 10)
  - SARS, April 2003 (Box 10)
  - SAT, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 10)
  - SB 358, Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Schneider, Bill, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Scholarship of Teaching and Learning, March 2003 (Box 10)
  - Scholarships, March 2003 (Box 10)
  - School of Medicine Alumni Day, April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Science Coalition, Feb.-Dec. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Semler, Jerry, March-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Senate Finance Committee, Feb. 25, 2003 (Box 10)
  - SE Reciprocal Agreement, undated (Box 10)
  - SES/SIS Group, May 2003 (Box 10)
  - SEVIS, April 9, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Shaw, Debora, April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Sherrill, Tony, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Shivey & Shoulders Show, April-May 2003 (Box 10)
    Includes VHS tape
  - Short, John, Feb.-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Sideli, Kathleen, March-April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Curt Simic Letters, Nov. 2002-March 2003 (Box 10)
  - Simon, Diane, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Simpson, Vi, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 10)
  - SLIS (School of Library and Information Science), April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Smith-Andrew, Kathy, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Social Work, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Souder, Mark, July 21, 2003 (Box 10)
  - SPEA (School of Public and Environmental Affairs), Feb.-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Spechler, Martin, Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Spirit of Philanthropy, April-May 2003 (Box 10)
  - Spirit of the Prairie Awards, April 2003 (Box 10)
  - Springer, Steve, June 2003 (Box 10)
  - Srivastava, Carolyn, March-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Staff Advance Agenda's and Summaries, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Standards for Success, Feb. 2003 (Box 10)
  - Stanfield, John, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 10)
  - Star Editorial Board, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - State Budget Committee, Nov. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - State of Diversity, Jan. 2003 (Box 10)
  - State of the University (Box 10)
    - March 13, 2003 (Box 10)
    - undated (Box 10)
  - State Relations, Office of, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 10)
  - Stephan, Bill, Dec. 2002-July 2003 (Box 11)
  - Stephens, Eric, May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Stevenson, Michael, March-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Strange, Georgia, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Strategic Hiring Initiative, Nov-Dec. 2002 (Box 11)
  - Strategic Plan, IUB, Dec. 2002 (Box 11)
  - Student Association (IUSA), April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Student Fee Bonds, Jan. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Student Problems, March-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Subbaswamy, Kumble, Nov. 2002-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Sullivan, Cheryl, Jan. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Summers, Phil, March-April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Surgery Chair, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Surveys, Feb.-Sept. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Sutter, Bob, April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Swimming, Jan. and March 2003 (Box 11)
  - Sylvia's Notes, Jan. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Sympathy & Memorial Resolutions, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 11)
  - T, general, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tarr, Anthony, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Taylor, Joseph, Manuscript, June 2003 (Box 11)
  - Teaching Awards, Jan. 2003 (Box 11)
  - The Teaching Company, June 2003 (Box 11)
  - Technology Partnership, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tempel, Gene, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Ten Preliminary Points for an Interim Administration, undated (Box 11)
  - Terrorism, March 2003 (Box 11)
  - Thorin, Suzanne, Jan.-March 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tinney, James, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tobias Report, May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Torke, Jim, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Toschlog, Ingrid, Feb. and May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Towfigi, Shah, March 13, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Toxicology Facility, Jan. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tranini, Gene, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Trustees, Indiana University Board of (Box 11)
    - General, Nov. 2002-March 2003 (Box 11)
    - Current, June 2003 (Box 11)
    - Ex Session, April-May 2003 (Box 11)
    - Finance and Audit Committee, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 11)
    - Good News, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
    - Meeting (Box 11)
      - (IUB), Jan. 30-31, 2003 (Box 11)
      - (IUB), Feb. 27-28, 2003 (Box 11)
      - April 3-4, 2003 (Box 11)
      - (IUB), May 7-9, 2003 (Box 11)
      - June 26-27, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Policies on Fee Approval, March 2003 (Box 11)
    - Salaries, Nov. 2002 (Box 11)
    - UFC, Feb.-March 2003 (Box 11)
    - Update, Dec. 2002-April 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tucker, Randy, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Tuition, March-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - Turk, Eleanor, Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - Turner, Eric, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 11)
  - U, general, April 2003; undated (Box 11)
  - UDG, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 11)
  - United Way, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 11)
  - University Affirmative Action Officer, July 2003 (Box 11)
  - University Ceremonies, undated (Box 11)
  - University Counsel, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 11)
  - University Faculty Council (UFC) (Box 11)
    - General, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 11)
    - Agenda Committee, March 2003 (Box 11)
  - University Information Technology Services (UITS), May 1998-Dec. 2002 (Box 11)
  - University Information Technology Services (UITS), Jan.-May 2003; undated (Box 12)
  - University Place Conference Center and Hotel, Jan.-May 2003 (Box 12)
  - Urban Initiatives, Jan.; undated (Box 12)
  - V, general, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Vice President (Box 12)
    - Administration, May-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Bloomington/Chancellor, Dec. 2002-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Budget & Financial Planning, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Diversity, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 12)
    - Information Technology, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Public Affairs & Government Relations (PAGR) and Special Counsel to the President, March-July 2003 (Box 12)
  - Vincennes University, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Visclosky, Rep., July 2003 (Box 12)
  - Vision, Indiana (IN Vision) Dinner, Dec. 18, 2002; (4 folders) (Box 12)
    (Restricted file removed from folder 4)
  - Vision for Indiana, Dec. 2002-Jan. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Vital Speeches, June 2003 (Box 12)
  - W, general, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Walda, John, Dec. 2002-June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Walker, George, Dec. 2002-March 2003 (Box 12)
  - Walker, Kim, Nov. 2002-July 2003 (Box 12)
  - Weatherwax, Tom, Jan. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Weaver, Don (Box 12)
    - General, Dec. 2002-May 2003 (Box 12)
    - Comments, Jan. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wells, Herman, 1999 (Box 12)
  - WFIU Commentary, Jan.-April 2003 (Box 12)
  - White, Dustin, Feb. 2003 (Box 12)
  - White, Kirk, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wilbern Report, undated (Box 12)
  - Wilkerson, Mike, Jan. and April 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wilkes, David S., May 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wokeck, Marianne, May 19, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wolfson, Lester, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Wong, Desmond, Feb. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Worldwide Friendship Association, Feb.-April 2003 (Box 12)
  - Yoshizato, Katsutoshi, June 2003 (Box 12)
  - Young, Michael, Dec. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Yurtseven, Oner, Jan. 2003 (Box 12)
  - Z, general, March-July 2003 (Box 12)
  - Alpha Files (Box 12)
    - A, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ba-Bd, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Be-Bk, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Bl-Bq, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Br-Bz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ca-Ce, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Cf-Cl, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Cm-Co, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Cp-Cz, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Da-Dd, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - De-Dh, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Di-Dz, April-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - E, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 12)
    - Fa-Fi, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Fo-Fz, Feb.-June 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ga-Gd, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ge-Gk, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Gl-Gq, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Gr-Gz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Has-Hh, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Hi-Hm, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Hn-Hz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - I, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - J, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Jones, Stan, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ka-Kh, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ki-Kn, April-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ko-Kz, Jan.-June 2003 (Box 12)
    - La-Ld, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Le-Ln, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Lo-Lz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ma-Mb, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Mc-Md, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Me-Mn, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Mo-Mz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - N, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - O, March-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - O'Bannon, Frank, July 2003 (Box 12)
    - P-Pd, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Pe-Pk, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Pl-Pz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Q, July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ra-Rg, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Rh-Rn, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ro-Rz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Sa-Sc, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Sd-Si, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Sk-Ss, April-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - St-Sz, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - T, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - U, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - V, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Wa-Wd, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - We-Wg, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Wh-Wi, Jan.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Wj-Wz, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Y, Feb.-July 2003 (Box 12)
    - Z, April-July 2003 (Box 12)
  - Chronological correspondence, January - April 2003 (Box 12)
- Restricted Files (Box 13)